<schemalist>
<!-- Base Schema for gnome Orca. This schema is not relocatable-->
<schema id="org.gnome.Orca" gettext-domain="Orca" path="/apps/gnome/Orca/">
  <key name="active-profile" type="as">
      <default>["Default", "default"]</default>
      <summary>Active profile</summary>
      <description>Current active profile.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="starting-profile" type="as">
      <default>["Default", "default"]</default>
      <summary>Starting profile</summary>
      <description>Current active profile that will be used at start.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="available-profiles" type="as">                                         
      <default>["default"]</default>
      <summary>Available Orca profiles</summary>
      <description>Current available Orca profiles.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="first-start" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>First Start Key</summary>
      <description>Indicates if it is the first time that orca runs.</description>
  </key>
  <child schema="org.gnome.Orca.Settings" name="settings"/>
</schema>

<schema id="org.gnome.Orca.Settings" gettext-domain="Orca">
  <!-- Magnifier related settings -->
  <key name="mag-edge-margin" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-edge-margin key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-edge-margin key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-pointer-follows-focus" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-pointer-follows-focus key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-pointer-follows-focus key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-text-tracking-mode" type="i">
    <default>2</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-text-tracking-mode key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-text-tracking-mode key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-pointer-follows-zoomer" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-pointer-follows-zoomer key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-pointer-follows-zoomer key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-cursor-color" type="s">
    <default>"#000000"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-cursor-color key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-cursor-color key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-zoomer-type" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-zoomer-type key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-zoomer-type key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-mag-zoom-color-inversion" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-mag-color-inversion key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-mag-color-inversion key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-cursor-size" type="i">
    <default>32</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-cursor-size key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-cursor-size key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-smoothing-mode" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-smoothing-mode key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-smoothing-mode key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-mag-cross-hair" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-mag-cross-hair key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-mag-cross-hair key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-zoomer-left" type="i">
    <default>512</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-zoomer-left key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-zoomer-left key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-zoomer-right" type="i">
    <default>1024</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-zoomer-right key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-zoomer-right key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-cross-hair-color" type="s">
    <default>"#000000"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-cross-hair-color key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-cross-hair-color key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-target-display" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-target-display key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-target-display key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-contrast-level" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-contrast-level key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-contrast-level key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-brightness-level-green" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-brightness-level-green key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-brightness-level-green key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-mouse-tracking-mode" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-mouse-tracking-mode key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-mouse-tracking-mode key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-zoomer-top" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-zoomer-top key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-zoomer-top key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-source-display" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-source-display key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-source-display key.</description>
  </key>
   <key name="mag-zoomer-border-size" type="i">
     <default>1</default>
     <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-zoomer-border-size key</summary>
     <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-zoomer-border-size key.</description>
   </key>
  <key name="mag-contrast-level-green" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-contrast-level-green key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-contrast-level-green key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-hide-cursor" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-hide-cursor key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-hide-cursor key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-zoomer-border-color" type="s">
    <default>"#000000"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-zoomer-border-color key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-zoomer-border-color key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-brightness-level-red" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-brightness-level-red key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-brightness-level-red key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-zoom-factor" type="d">
    <default>4.0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-zoom-factor key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-zoom-factor key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-cross-hair-size" type="i">
    <default>16</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-cross-hair-size key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-cross-hair-size key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-brightness-level-blue" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-brightness-level-blue key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-brightness-level-blue key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-mag-zoomer-border" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-mag-zoomer-border key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-mag-zoomer-border key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-control-tracking-mode" type="i">
    <default>2</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-control-tracking-mode key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-control-tracking-mode key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-zoomer-bottom" type="i">
    <default>768</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-zoomer-bottom key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-zoomer-bottom key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-contrast-level-blue" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-contrast-level-blue key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-contrast-level-blue key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-contrast-level-red" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-contrast-level-red key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-contrast-level-red key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-color-filtering-mode" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-color-filtering-mode key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-color-filtering-mode key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mag-brightness-level" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mag-brightness-level key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mag-brightness-level key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-mag-cross-hair-clip" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-mag-cross-hair-clip key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-mag-cross-hair-clip key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-mag-cursor" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-mag-cursor key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-mag-cursor key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-mag-cursor-explicit-size" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-mag-cursor-explicit-size key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-mag-cursor-explicit-size key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-mag-live-updating" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-mag-live-updating key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-mag-live-updating key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-magnifier" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-magnifier key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-magnifier key.</description>
  </key>
  <!-- Braille related settings -->
  <key name="enable-contracted-braille" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-contracted-braille key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-contracted-braille key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-braille" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-braille key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-braille key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-braille-grouping" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-braille-grouping key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-braille-grouping key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enabled-brailled-text-attributes" type="s">
    <default>"size:; family-name:; weight:400; indent:0; underline:none; strikethrough:false; justification:left; style:normal; text-spelling:none;"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enabled-brailled-text-attributes key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enabled-brailled-text-attributes key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-indicator-attrib" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-indicator-attrib key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-indicator-attrib key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-rolename-style" type="i">
    <default>1</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-rolename-style key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-rolename-style key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-braille-monitor" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-braille-monitor key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-braille-monitor key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-braille-context" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-braille-context key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-braille-context key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="disable-braille-end-of-line" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for disable-braille-end-of-line key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for disable-braille-end-of-line key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-flash-time" type="i">
    <default>5000</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-flash-time key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-flash-time key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-selector-indicator" type="i">
    <default>192</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-selector-indicator key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-selector-indicator key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-link-indicator" type="i">
    <default>192</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-link-indicator key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-link-indicator key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-verbosity-level" type="i">
    <default>1</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-verbosity-level key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-verbosity-level key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-end-of-line-indicator" type="s">
    <default>" $l"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-end-of-line-indicator key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-end-of-line-indicator key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-required-state-string" type="s">
    <default>"requerido"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-required-state-string key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-required-state-string key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-contraction-table" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-contraction-table key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-contraction-table key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="braille-alignment-style" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for braille-alignment-style key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for braille-alignment-style key.</description>
  </key>
  <!-- Keys related settings -->
  <key name="enable-diacritical-keys" type="b">                                         
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-diacritical-keys key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-diacritical-keys key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-navigation-keys" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-navigation-keys key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-navigation-keys key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-locking-keys" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-locking-keys key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-locking-keys key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-function-keys" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-function-keys key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-function-keys key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-printable-keys" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-printable-keys key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-printable-keys key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="orca-modifier-keys" type="as">
    <default>['Insert', 'Kp-insert']</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for orca-modifier-keys key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for orca-modifier-keys key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-modifier-keys" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-modifier-keys key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-modifier-keys key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-action-keys" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-action-keys key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-action-keys key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-key-echo" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-key-echo key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-key-echo key.</description>
  </key>
  <!-- TODO: Group all these another settings-->
  <key name="speak-cell-span" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for speak-cell-span key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for speak-cell-span key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="progress-bar-update-interval" type="i">
    <default>10</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for progress-bar-update-interval key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for progress-bar-update-interval key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="speak-cell-coordinates" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for speak-cell-coordinates key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for speak-cell-coordinates key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-pause-breaks" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-pause-breaks key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-pause-breaks key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="speak-blank-lines" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for speak-blank-lines key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for speak-blank-lines key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="keyboard-layout" type="i">
    <default>1</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for keyboard-layout key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for keyboard-layout key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="verbalize-punctuation-style" type="i">
    <default>1</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for verbalize-punctuation-style key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for verbalize-punctuation-style key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="progress-bar-verbosity" type="i">
    <default>1</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for progress-bar-verbosity key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for progress-bar-verbosity key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-speech" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-speech key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-speech key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-mnemonic-speaking" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-mnemonic-speaking key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-mnemonic-speaking key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="read-table-cell-row" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for read-table-cell-row key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for read-table-cell-row key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="speech-split-multi-case" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for speech-split-multi-case key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for speech-split-multi-case key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="message-verbosity-level" type="i">
    <default>1</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for message-verbosity-level key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for message-verbosity-level key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-speech-indentation" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-speech-indentation key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-speech-indentation key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="mouse-dwell-delay" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for mouse-dwell-delay key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for mouse-dwell-delay key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="chat-speak-room-name" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for chat-speak-room-name key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for chat-speak-room-name key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="speech-server-factory" type="s">
    <default>"speechdispatcherfactory"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for speech-server-factory key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for speech-server-factory key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="speech-server-info" type="as">
    <default>['', '']</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for speech-server-factory key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for speech-server-factory key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-echo-by-character" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-echo-by-character key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-echo-by-character key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="flash-verbosity-level" type="i">
    <default>1</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for flash-verbosity-level key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for flash-verbosity-level key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-flash-messages" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-flash-messages key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-flash-messages key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="present-tool-tips" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for present-tool-tips key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for present-tool-tips key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="flash-is-persistent" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for flash-is-persistent key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for flash-is-persistent key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="large-object-text-length" type="i">
    <default>75</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for large-object-text-length key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for large-object-text-length key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-echo-by-sentence" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-echo-by-sentence key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-echo-by-sentence key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enabled-spoken-text-attributes" type="s">
    <default>"size:; family-name:; weight:400; indent:0; underline:none; strikethrough:false; justification:left; style:normal; paragraph-style:; text-spelling:none;"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enabled-spoken-text-attributes key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enabled-spoken-text-attributes key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="chat-message-verbosity" type="i">
    <default>0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for chat-message-verbosity key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for chat-message-verbosity key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="present-time-format" type="s">
    <default>"%X"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for present-time-format key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for present-time-format key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="present-required-state" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for present-required-state key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for present-required-state key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="speak-cell-headers" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for speak-cell-headers key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for speak-cell-headers key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="speech-verbosity-level" type="i">
    <default>1</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for speech-verbosity-level key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for speech-verbosity-level key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="speech-required-state-string" type="s">
    <default>"requerido"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for speech-required-state-string key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for speech-required-state-string key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="chat-announce-buddy-typing" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for chat-announce-buddy-typing key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for chat-announce-buddy-typing key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="quit-orca-no-confirmation" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for quit-orca-no-confirmation key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for quit-orca-no-confirmation key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-progress-bar-updates" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-progress-bar-updates key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-progress-bar-updates key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-echo-by-word" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-echo-by-word key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-echo-by-word key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-position-speaking" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-position-speaking key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-position-speaking key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="only-speak-displayed-text" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for only-speak-displayed-text key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for only-speak-displayed-text key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="wrapped-structural-navigation" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for wrapped-structural-navigation key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for wrapped-structural-navigation key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="skip-blank-cells" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for skip-blank-cells key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for skip-blank-cells key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="chat-room-histories" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for chat-room-histories key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for chat-room-histories key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="show-main-window" type="b">
    <default>true</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for show-main-window key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for show-main-window key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="say-all-style" type="i">
    <default>1</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for say-all-style key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for say-all-style key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-tutorial-messages" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-tutorial-messages key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-tutorial-messages key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="enable-mouse-review" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for enable-mouse-review key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for enable-mouse-review key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="present-date-format" type="s">
    <default>"%x"</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for present-date-format key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for present-date-format key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="profile" type="as">
    <default>['Default', 'default']</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="available-pronunciations" type="as">
    <default>[]</default>
    <summary>Available Pronunciations</summary>
    <description>This list contains all available pronunciations for this settings' owner</description>
  </key>
  <key name="available-keybindings" type="as">
    <default>[]</default>
    <summary>Available Keybindings</summary>
    <description>This list contains all available keybindings for this settings' owner</description>
  </key>
  <child schema="org.gnome.Orca.Settings.Voices" name="voices"/>
  <child schema="org.gnome.Orca.Settings.Pronunciations" name="pronunciations"/>
  <child schema="org.gnome.Orca.Settings.Keybindings" name="keybindings"/>
</schema>
<schema id="org.gnome.Orca.Settings.Voices" gettext-domain="Orca">
  <key name="established" type="b">
    <default>false</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="average-pitch" type="d">
    <default>5.0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="gain" type="d">
    <default>10.0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="rate" type="d">
    <default>50.0</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <child schema="org.gnome.Orca.Settings.Voices.Family" name="family"/>
</schema>
<schema id="org.gnome.Orca.Settings.Voices.Family" gettext-domain="Orca">
  <key name="name" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="locale" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="gender" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
</schema>
<schema id="org.gnome.Orca.Settings.Pronunciations" gettext-domain="Orca">
  <key name="word" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="pronunciation" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
</schema>
<schema id="org.gnome.Orca.Settings.Keybindings" gettext-domain="Orca">
  <key name="modifier-mask" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="default-modifier-mask" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="handler" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="click" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="modifier-mask-alt" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="default-modifier-mask-alt" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="handler-alt" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>
  <key name="click-alt" type="s">
    <default>""</default>
    <summary>TODO: Add a summary for profile key</summary>
    <description>TODO: Add a description for profile key.</description>
  </key>

</schema>


</schemalist>
